<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
		<!--	created with www.mysitemapgenerator.com	-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
	<channel>
		<title>Khan Engineering and Screen Print</title>
		<link><![CDATA[https://khanengineerings.com]]></link>
		<description>Khan Engineering is leading Manufacturer of Screen Printing Machinery's in Pakistan. Each and every machine are MADE IN PAKISTAN!! Khan Engineering stands as a pioneering force in the realm of screen printing machinery, renowned for its unwavering commitment to excellence since its inception. With a rich history steeped in innovation, our company has continually pushed the boundaries of technology to deliver cutting-edge solutions to the global market.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<generator>MySitemapGenerator (www.mysitemapgenerator.com)</generator>

		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">4020864821</guid>
			<title>Get A Quotation</title>
			<link>https://khanengineerings.com/Get%20Quotation</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>Khan Engineering is leading Manufacturer of Screen Printing Machinery's in Pakistan. Each and every machine are MADE IN PAKISTAN!!. Get Instant Quotation by Contacting Us!!</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Getting a quotation from Khan Engineering is a simple and hassle-free process. Just reach out to us through our contact channels, and our responsive team will guide you through the quotation process. Whether you have a specific list of equipment in mind or need assistance in choosing the right solutions, we're here to help.</p><h1>Feel Free To Ask a Quotation</h1><p>Feel free to share your project details, specifications, and any specific requirements you may have. Our team will promptly provide you with a comprehensive quotation, ensuring clarity and transparency in every step of the process.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:11:25 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png" type="image/png" length="0" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">371742862</guid>
			<title>Machine Parts</title>
			<link>https://khanengineerings.com/Machine%20Parts</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>Khan Engineering is leading Manufacturer of Screen Printing Machinery's in Pakistan. Each and every machine are MADE IN PAKISTAN!!. We also Provide Machine parts!!.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Feel empowered to make your machine parts purchase at Khan Engineering with absolute confidence. Our user-friendly interface and comprehensive product information make browsing and selecting the right components a breeze. With a commitment to customer satisfaction, we assure you of a seamless and satisfying buying experience. Explore our diverse catalog, confident that you're choosing quality and reliability from a trusted industry leader.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:11:25 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png" type="image/png" length="0" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">3236303043</guid>
			<title>Flasher Cure Units</title>
			<link>https://khanengineerings.com/Equipment</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Round Screen Printing Machine is tailored for cylindrical objects, offering automated precision in applying graphics around their surfaces. With rotational capabilities, it ensures seamless and efficient printing on items like bottles and containers.</p><h2>Heat Press Printing</h2><p>Heat presses utilize heat and pressure to transfer designs onto various surfaces, making them essential tools for creating durable and vibrant prints on materials like fabrics, ceramics, and metals. Available in different types, such as clamshell and swing-away models, they offer versatility and efficiency in the printing process.</p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/Heat%20Presses.jpeg"></p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/UVCuring.jpg"></p><h2>Uv Curing for Printing</h2><p>UV curing in screen printing machines employs ultraviolet light to quickly and precisely cure inks, resulting in vibrant and durable prints on various surfaces. This technology ensures fast drying times and enhanced print quality, making it a valuable asset for efficient and high-quality screen printing.</p><h2>CNC Machine</h2><p>We Also Manufacture CNC Machines. CNC Machines for Carving Wood like Door, Aluminium, Silver. It can also do engraving with Laser like Cutting Metal, Engraving on Wood or Metal, Sewing Clothes.</p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/Soon.jpg"></p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/ScreenExposingCamera.jpg"></p><h2>Printing Screen Exposing Camera</h2><p>Exposing Camera are Used To Expose Designs To the Printing Screen by using UV Light Exposure. We can Also Manufacture and Provide you that.</p><p>At Khan Engineering, our commitment to excellence extends to every aspect of our service. With a team of dedicated experts, we pride ourselves on delivering unparalleled support tailored to your engineering needs.</p><p>Our technical specialists are here to provide insightful solutions, answer your queries, and guide you through any challenges you may encounter. Khan Engineering Support is your trusted partner on the journey to achieving engineering excellence.</p><p>Contact us today to experience firsthand the proactive and personalized assistance that sets Khan Engineering Support apart. Your success is our priority, and we're here to ensure your engineering endeavors thrive with our unwavering support.</p><h3>Khan Engineering & Printing Machine Manufacturer</h3><p>Khan Engineering is a trusted name in precision engineering and screen printing machine manufacturing. With a legacy of quality craftsmanship, we deliver innovative solutions tailored to industry needs. Our state-of-the-art facility and skilled team ensure top-notch reliability and performance. Elevate your screen printing business with Khan Engineering's excellence and innovation.</p><h3>Equipments</h3><p><a href="https://khanengineerings.com/">Automatic Screen Printing Machine</a></p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png"></p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo_only.png"></p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:11:25 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1746064843</guid>
			<title>Contact Us</title>
			<link>https://khanengineerings.com/Contact</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Get in touch with us! Whether you have questions, feedback, or just want to say hello, our Contact Us page is the gateway to reaching our friendly team. Fill out the form, drop us an email, or connect through social media. We're here to assist you!</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:11:24 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">3810282736</guid>
			<title>Photos and Videos of Screen Printing Machine by Khan Engineering and Screen Print</title>
			<link>https://khanengineerings.com/Gallery</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>Khan Engineering is leading Manufacturer of Screen Printing Machinery's in Pakistan. Gallery of our Equipments we made in Pakistan</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Khan Engineering is a trusted name in precision engineering and screen printing machine manufacturing. With a legacy of quality craftsmanship, we deliver innovative solutions tailored to industry needs. Our state-of-the-art facility and skilled team ensure top-notch reliability and performance. Elevate your screen printing business with Khan Engineering's excellence and innovation.</p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png"></p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo_only.png"></p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:11:24 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png" type="image/png" length="0" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">897774046</guid>
			<title>Want to Upgrade Gear With Khan Engineering ?</title>
			<link>https://khanengineerings.com/About</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>Khan Engineering is leading Manufacturer of Screen Printing Machinery's in Pakistan. Each and every machine are MADE IN PAKISTAN!! Khan Engineering is a premier manufacturer of cutting-edge screen printing machinery. With a commitment to innovation and precision, we deliver top-quality equipment trusted by industries worldwide. Our products blend advanced technology with reliability, empowering businesses to achieve exceptional results in their printing processes.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Khan Engineering is a trusted name in precision engineering and screen printing machine manufacturing. With a legacy of quality craftsmanship, we deliver innovative solutions tailored to industry needs. Our state-of-the-art facility and skilled team ensure top-notch reliability and performance. Elevate your screen printing business with Khan Engineering's excellence and innovation.</p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png"></p><p><img src="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo_only.png"></p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:11:25 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://khanengineerings.com/assets/logo.png" type="image/png" length="0" />
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>